You intend to see it angry, but one scene finds yourself all for
someone who can’t see it, what if this is you, this
video is you.  Hello everyone abnormal, I'm Ming, I
finally want to take pictures, I and the team,
immediately entered the venue to see the left turn.  Familiar ря style
Christopher Len knows it, shoot
gas from the cool and tell you can not be at any time at the beginning of this to play when the chest
plastic crazy burning guy, for no do not throw
wear a bottom first.  Here's a story, the original author
Homorkma has two gods given to the work frame is talking
about the second and this episode we will not spoil, we will talk about the
previous first book Elliot, Iliad please
after reading this understand the key characters of the film branch and
worldview.  If you like this material, add a no number a fire face in the comments and
you will know.  What was the cause of the 10-year Trojan War and
how did he set the background of this story
?  Which of the famous Trojans
are myths and which ones are real?
Time turned back before the 12th century young and contemporary of the late
we go here, it was called selling stone civilization selling
senianGree here more mountains and flat land less large
produced a group of extremely using
valve kings.  What about among these people?  The bus one was called
[music] plus the
Greek circles at that time were actually a fire barrel that could explode at any time
.  Why for this woman
Helen all asked her is the
daughter of mortal life, the most beautiful in Greece is her the king this
is fighting to marry the moment seeing back the big exposed rough this fighting girl fighting to be about to
split friends quickly bully the great civil war at this time this our
protagonist has no choice to appear, trying to put this international 9
points ah.  Boo was the king of Isa, and he was not as big as the other kings
, but in terms of turns no one in all Greece was saved fast.  Sometimes
for a fight Helen fights against the face, anytime a fight up,
my Desi walked out to be a peacemaker, now the last line is absolutely good.
So we decided by drawing signatures, but before that, we have to make
a poisonous boy first scare, no matter who the god of luck chose in the end
[music] good, if the day has a pink intestine to mess with his
wife, we all Greek brothers together to depressed him, this
trick once the crisis is lifted, in the end, Helen married, as I
said earlier, the worst boss in Greece
.
Well, the eggs are removed on this side of Greece, and we will pass the test
a little bit and look across the sea.
That's Troy.
Hey, being a weapon requires quarrying. This is the only way to ore mines
, so Troy is really the first.  At first there was
no great favor on this side of Greece and Troy, the
King of Troy also sent his second early Paris to go to Bada for a
diplomatic visit, to the stunned one.  Let this be this
diplomacy out of the big hair
Pa even in people's map, and Siba King Helen this
[music]
crush He also folded Helens ran back to Tei feed, people invited
[music] dinner, you folded someone else's wife, this hat came from
the beginning to the prince of Sba [music].  Well,
naturally they got one of his Agamen to complain, on the surface
he was angry and had to help his brother out.  But in
practice, to this opportunity owner, this thing is simply the
eldest daughter from the sky.  The
kind of wealth that this guy is so rich about, actually, has been with him for a long time
.  The leg immediately got back a good received that Seyan to the maximum number,
like the king of all [music] Greece.  Hey, you guys have been having
sex to fight special.  That's why for a green hat a line easy to walk
first this ancient world war 咧, officially broke out
Ming-hyun letter ah but the problem is the whole of Greece no king is
sincerely on the field.  In the end, for people's couple's home market
to die, the most striking of the de just done
ascites rotten, crazy know is of course the suitor Yan Zheng that is he
ছা out of it, add strength to fight back kind of themselves, in
order to avoid the war this he decided.
He pulled the two unpulled beasts together.  It was
supposed to stop at the killing of species, they are killing.  The soldiers came to the
door originally?  See wow, the friend stupid is looking for another one
, but the leader this see through his pretend overnight to grab
his newborn put in front of the car can not be received no matter how good
, grandfather Ben broke out, with all his strength so the sea two animals
are avoiding the child?  The boy is fine, but the movie
can't stop thinking.
After the smartest one has to find the best draw that example says to win this
game must find the invulnerable God of War Keely.
That's Achilles this is only 10 years old, but my
mother was afraid that she would die in battle, so she had to hide
[music] in her statement
.  Princess Zheng returned to fly away
, is a big good, one hand is drawn up, who walks up to
you cut whom?
Such a big street jump, even if I want to cover it up, I can't hide Achillesley's
entry into the team.
Bones, one by one, the Greek coalition officially set off, 100,000
troops over a thousand
[music]
mortals born after, the fighting power exploded
exaggerated d is the ancient revenge of this alliance.  Teyi
will soon know how crazy these people are
of the killing beach, the opposite actually early shock, Wan thought even the
lark.
You know, as soon as the Greek troops landed it was a holocaust.
One of the generals even broke through the blood dew.  And Akilee
sees a very clear and invulnerable image in the Trump army.  Directly use the
headband to live and die.  The Teyi army ಯ formed an army, all
died and lived at the gate.  The stuffed [music] red A-men thought, after
seeing this, a few months can finish work and grab it back
.  But they simply did not know that the whole game of Teruo
was actually a shoulderless rush of central pole defense.
[Music]
Why can't a 100,000-strong army beat in?  Got to count it
, found this game on no fight at all, specially down the airport this
is late to crazy ah, the legend is by Apollo and Hai personally hands
, [music] in the young and contemporary head shot machine has not been invented,
hard gut on one is dead one.  What made him even more headache was that the
people in Tello were very pumped.  Troy troops still
have plenty of allies, with his army dead hand is the old country
[music] king Pumos, and his eldest son Lord Tanger
and the beach army
wife has children know the younger brother made a big head big
brother has gone up to protect the homeland  The
initial children's blood this has been worn away is just the psychological curve points
twisted
work into will be in the surrounding villages to it.  Achilles herself took the
lead in escaping the 23 innocent people.  The
heroes who were fighting for Yao చ్ turned into a group of women fighting
Nipin divided their own people beat their own beasts
.  What about?  He is not down anyway sex white not
beat yourself beat him yourself when you beat you do not come back begging me
living next to receive this anti-white eyes against the back of the head yeah the whole army you
life and death fighting nine years the boss even for the girl fighting face
turtle.   The
emperor of Tei saw the opportunity to immediately talk to
Lap army was instantly ice fish raw to be pressed all the way to the seaside
even the big boss Asians were scared and said to drive away, so that the
next d make this fly into the sky.
Another is the big [music] people rushing to spin next to prepare to release, the
ship of a hundred thousand troops can never return to the incense.   Ah
Ka-men
handed over his seat.  God, no matter how you answer, you have a taste. He said you are dead
.
However, he is a world-playing brother, it is always not able to
do death soon boldly left the God of War specifications to bring Manchester City A
Kelis or on the
Di army a look at the armor this, thought the war horse this immediately arrived.   The
Greek United military gas-blasted star, chasing Mann all the way, but chasing
one too accurately, this good brother, was
killed by a spear team in the melee.  The death of a good brother was reported back to the military camp Kilis immediately went
crazy. The one who died was not an ordinary soldier, but his
bestfriend.  It's also rumored to be someone else.   At
the moment he scored these two words in his mind.  Boo takes revenge.
Akilis re-entered the field, killed to the army
horizontal cheating things, special disembarkation army this, all back in, left one
man this, choose to be outside and single jump.  Hector
.   In the
two duels, Achilles completely overwhelmed this one prince of Trojan
.  Zo he has not been involved enough, Achlys is even
tied to the back of the chariot, pocketing the whole madness dragged for
12 days
this kind of tongue behavior, finally revealed the gods in the sky
.  A solo fighter in the god of attack sitting under the aid of this,
by the Duke of Paris a while precision shot
Liz's foot bandage.  [Scream]
Legend has it that when Alis was born, this mother soaked in famous water, so that
he could not be shot, was his mother pulled his heel
[music] did not submerge in the water, became the only dead in the whole body, also
within the English.
A generation of war spirits and gods of war were just like this, and Fang
fell into it again.   The
warriors came to the 10th year, the Greek army this suddenly rebelled,
[music] they went up the mountain ła made a giant Trojan
horse,
no Det with 300 elites this
bowed into the horse
Crying to say it, wow, the old Greeks want to kill my god, like
I can leave on this horse this is their sin offering Biamer
came, deliberately to so big this, is not want you to pull
into it.  The people of Tello were heartbroken when they heard this.  Even they are invincible. The whole
game is broken and a wooden horse enters.  That night, Tello
healed all ah fell into madness 10 years, finally waited for the Greeks to
vote away, everyone drink tablets sleep dead pigs but they do not
know they pulled in this is not a fetish, is dead
Tens of thousands of Greek troops seemed to flocked of hunger
, 10 years of forehead completely red, see laughter, strong people to cut,
not
a second still teaching, the next temple has reached out, the whole civilian
area for a sea of ​​​​fire, old rich things scream
Princess, andra hugged the god Athena to
avoid broken, the Greek collar this for the prison hard, pulled her
hair, dragged her out of the stronghold.  Roughly follow the roots, they
snatched the bb has a whole order down to
this city overnight as accurate, ten years of Troy
War, is so officially ended.
This story, to the ancients this is like biblical
embodiment [music].  Taking a bare foot so showed
how dark human nature can be in the face of war.  And how high are the gods in the sky
,
indispensable, in the 19th century there was a crazy old [music]
businessman named Sleeman, who was carrying a book of the myth of the hippopotamus
, and treated the treasure hunter as the earth rider who dug the ground.  The result
really allowed him to discover Troy and opened the door to the world of learning
.  Hey, although his technique was very rough, and he even blew
through the formation that was really in the Trojan War.  But as evidence
, the city of Troy really existed and was destroyed by big goods
.  Learning currently generally agrees with [music] about 3200
years ago here it happened and frame.  V
's [music]
system, yes, and
unearthed ancient diplomatic boards.  These white and black bases are named
There is strong documentary evidence that there was probably a war between them and the [music] Greeks for
a map called, the map of Troy
.  What's even more amazing is that the name of the Chief Executive is written on it
, which is exactly
the same as Alexander, the real name of Paris in the myth.
Since both Troy and the war are likely true.  So is the
100,000-strong army really going to die for the top?  Scholars speculate that
this motive may not be true. It was the Greek army to
seize the streets and treasures of the Dadali Haihe.  So why did some
history end up being myths?  Ya we have to understand, what about
after the Trojan War?  Greece has been through the dark age of [music] for
400 years, relying on a bag of
people's verbal quotient, slowly
condensed and sublimated into a private war full of divine colors.
So how to explain the most famous eye horse?  History mainly has
two good speculations, first, it is not actually a horse
, but a step used to hit the help of a rushing car but outsiders look
like a horse, so it was later mythologized.  Second, the coincidence
showed that Troy's invincible growth was actually likely to have been shattered by the ground shock
.  And on the Greek mythology side, the sea god Persedon
is the god of earthquakes, and his exclusive horse is just the
horse, so the horse
is just a myth of the ancients about an earthquake natural disaster.
Okay, let’s go back to the story, what happens to several of the main characters
?  The second Paris who engaged in this 10-year hell has been
warfare long before the apprenticeship, so
Allen escaped the night before Fman
layers, is taking a sword rushed in to chop him to death
, a look at his beautiful this even a second sinking [music]
, the sword fell,
As for Austro-Germany receiving this his end is much worse
.  Hao Cheng that night Greek death sick
god, he and the brothers on the way back crazy mouth talk, to go through
ten years of hell wandering, no mistake, this is exactly the
starting point of Christopher's anger at the beginning
, in other words, it is actually a road movie, the main line
is to see the miserable condemnation of not returning home
Friends who enter the venue together!  And what about 10pm this coming Sunday
?  I will open and share
Christopher's version exactly
how different from the original, if you are interested or want to share, remember to join
our membership.  Thinking you think the origin of this one because answer
it?  Or is it just for the sake of the road?  Leave a comment and let us
know.  Finally, if we want to be objective, we might as well
hit the ground objective
[music]
in
[music].